Guide to the Larry Rivers Papers 1952-2010 MSS 293
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Project Files
  - Subseries A: Artwork Tracking
    - [Inventory / Artwork Tracking], undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - [Inventory / Artwork Tracking], undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - [Inventory / Artwork Tracking], undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Inventory / Computer, 1988, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Inventory Log Book, 1994, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Inventory Log Book, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Inventory: Summer 1998 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Library / Photo Info, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Library, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - List of Stolen Goods / Artworks, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Loan Records, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Loan Records, 1989-1992 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Loan Records, 1989-1992 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Loan Records, 1989-1993 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Loan Records, 1990-1993 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Loan Records, 1990-1994 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Loan Records, 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Loan Records, 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Loans, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Loans / Consignments, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Museum Collections, 1987-88, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Museums, 1983-1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Paintings 1950s: Family Member Portraits, Cards, Washington Crossing the Delaware, Cedar Bar Menu, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Paintings 1950s: Family Member Portraits, Cards, Washington Crossing the Delaware, Cedar Bar Menu (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Paintings 1950s: Family Member Portraits, Cards, Washington Crossing the Delaware, Cedar Bar Menu (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Paintings 1950s: Various Portraits and Peoples and Various Crazy Canvases ("Pots + Pans", "2nd Avenue with 'The'"), etc., undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Paintings 1950s: Various Portraits and Peoples and Various Crazy Canvases ("Pots + Pans", "2nd Avenue with 'The'"), etc. (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Paintings 1960s: Anatomy Lessons, Dutch Masters, Websters, Washington Crossing the Delaware, French Money, Camels, Last Civil War Hero, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Paintings 1960s: Anatomy Lessons, Dutch Masters, Websters, Washington Crossing the Delaware, French Money, Camels, Last Civil War Hero (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Paintings 1960s: Anatomy Lessons, Dutch Masters, Websters, Washington Crossing the Delaware, French Money, Camels, Last Civil War Hero (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Paintings 1960s: Anatomy Lessons, Dutch Masters, Websters, Washington Crossing the Delaware, French Money, Camels, Last Civil War Hero (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Paintings 1960s: Dreyfus Lions, African Studies, Various Mixed Media, Various Portraits, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Paintings 1960s: Dreyfus Lions, African Studies, Various Mixed Media, Various Portraits (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Paintings 1960s: Dreyfus Lions, African Studies, Various Mixed Media, Various Portraits (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Paintings 1960s: Dreyfus Lions, African Studies, Various Mixed Media, Various Portraits (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Paintings 1960s: King of Hearts, Cezanne Stamp, N.Y. Film Festival, Disque Blue, Collaboration w/ K.K., Buick w/ a "P", Cedar Bar Menu, Daily Screw, Map of Italy, Lampman Loves It, Boston Massacre, Cozy Cole, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Paintings 1960s: King of Hearts, Cezanne Stamp, N.Y. Film Festival, Disque Blue, Collaboration w/ K.K., Buick w/ a "P", Cedar Bar Menu, Daily Screw, Map of Italy, Lampman Loves It, Boston Massacre, Cozy Cole (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Paintings 1970s: Websters, Dutch Masters, Rembrandt's Polish Rider, Wedding Photo, Japanese Series, undated (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Paintings 1970s: Websters, Dutch Masters, Rembrandt's Polish Rider, Wedding Photo, Japanese Series (cont'd), undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Paintings 1970s: Various Mixed Media, Portraits, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Paintings 1980s: Continuing Interest in Abstract Art, History of Matzah, Modernist Times, undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Paintings 1990s, undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Paintings, Mixed Media, & Sculpture, undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Photos / Artwork In / Out, 1984-1988 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - [Photos & Transparencies of Works for Sale], 1986, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Price Inquiries, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Prices, 1987, undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Prices of Artwork, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Prices of Artwork, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Print Info, 1990, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - The Print Project - written notes, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Prints Available for Sale, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Provenance, 1987-1989 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Release Forms & Condition Reports, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Sales & Commissions, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Sales Info, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1976-1982 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1987-94 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1990-1992 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1990-1994 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1990-1994 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1991-1995 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1993 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Sales & Loan Records, 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Sales & Loan Records, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Sales & Loan Records, 1999-2003 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Sales & Loan Records, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - [Sales & Loan Records], 2000-2002 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Sales & Loan Records, A, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Sales & Loan Records, B, 1989-1993 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Sales & Loan Records, B, 1989-1993 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Sales & Loan Records, B, 1989-1994 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Sales & Loan Records, C, 1991-1994 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Sales & Loan Records, D, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Sales & Loan Records, D, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Sales & Loan Records, D, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Sales & Loan Records, E - G, 1989-1994 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Sales & Loan Records, E - G, 1989-1994 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Sales & Loan Records, H - I, 1987-1994 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Sales & Loan Records, H - I, 1987-1994 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Sales & Loan Records, H - I, 1987-1994 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - [Sales Ledger], 1992, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - [Sales / Loan Ledger], 1982-1986 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - [Sales / Loan Ledger], 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Sales Money Due, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Sales Records, 1955-66, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Sales Records, 1957-1975 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Sales Records, 1970-1983 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Sales Records, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Sculpture 1950s: Berdie, John Myers, Masks, Steel Plant, Kabuki, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Shows/Prices, 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Slide List, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Slide Show Info, 12 Feb 1988 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Slides Out, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Slides, Photos, Loans Returned, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Slides, Photos, Loans Returned, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Slides Returned, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Studio Sales, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Work Letters Received (1 of 2), 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Work Letters Received (2 of 2), 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Works Before 1950, undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Works on Consignment, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - "Works For Sale, Old Lists", 1990-1992 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Works: General Info, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Works Info, 1989-90, undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Works Information - Prints and Inventory in Stock, 1986-87, undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Works on Loan, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Works Loaned & Returned, 1986-1989 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Works at the Louvre, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Works in Progress, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Works Receipts, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Works Returned, 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Works Returned, 1988-1991 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Works Shipped, Sold, 1990-1992 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Works Shipped, Sold, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Works Shipped, Sold, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Works Sold, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Works Sold, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: By Name
    Subseries B contains materials, organized by name (personal or organizational), related to the creative process and exhibition of Larry Rivers artworks.
    Materials are arranged alphabetically by title; within each folder, materials are in their original order. Folders with identical titles are arranged by date. Any titles inferred by the archivist are enclosed in square brackets.
    - The Allen Ginsberg Memorial Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Alveryd, Bo, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Arlene Bujese Gallery, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Ashbery, John (film project), 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Avallon Restaurant, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Bee County College, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Birmingham Bloomfield Art Association, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Brand X Editions, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Brandeis University, 1972, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Bristed-Manning Travel Service (travel to France), 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Budapest Cultural Forum, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Burnside, Susan, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Carol Publishing Group (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Casino Paradise, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Centre Georges Pompidou, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Chapin, Katherine, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank Art Program, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Clarkson N. Potter, Inc., Publishers, 1983-1999 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Columbo, Furio, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Corcoran Museum and School of Art, 1996-1998 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Corddry, Charlotte, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Cross, Mary, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Daniels, Myrna and John, 1989-1995 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Daniels, Myrna and John, 1989-1996 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - David Floria Gallery, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Desilets, Deborah, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - DiFiore, Andrea, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Duggal Transactions, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Dwan Gallery, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Earth Celebrations, 1995, undated (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Elaine Benson Gallery, 1987-1997 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Fay, Thomas, 1993-1995 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Feinstein, Stephen, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Fox, Irving, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - The Four Seasons Restaurant, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - The Functional Art Gallery, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Galerie Hertz, 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Gallery de la Tour, 1994-1996 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - GHJ Graphics Inc., 1980 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Gordon, Edward S., undated (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Gracie Mansion Gallery, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Graphische Sammlung, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Gresham Studio Ltd., 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Groffsky, Maxine, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Haft, Richard J., 1975-1981 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Harry Lillywhite & Son, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - Hebrew Union College - Jewish Institute of Religion, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Heckscher Museum, 1990, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Heland Thorden Wetterling Galleries, Stockholm, 1985-1987 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - Heland Thorden Wetterling Galleries, Stockholm (1 of 2), 1985-1993 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Heland Thorden Wetterling Galleries, Stockholm (2 of 2), 1985-1993 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Heland Thorden Wetterling Galleries, Stockholm, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Himelfarb, Louise, 1978-1984 (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Hirshhorn, Joseph, 1980-1984 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - Horn, Harry, 1975-1981 (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Horwitch, Elaine, 1987-1994 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Hotel Chelsea, 1995-1999 (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Hunter, Sam, 1987-88, undated (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - Hunter, Sam (1 of 6), 1987-92, undated (Box 37, Folder 66)
    - Hunter, Sam (2 of 6), 1987-92, undated (Box 37, Folder 67)
    - Hunter, Sam (3 of 6), 1987-92, undated (Box 37, Folder 68)
    - Hunter, Sam (4 of 6), 1987-92, undated (Box 37, Folder 69)
    - Hunter, Sam (5 of 6), 1987-92, undated (Box 37, Folder 70)
    - Hunter, Sam (6 of 6), 1987-92, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Hunter, Sam, 1987-1994 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Hunter, Sam, 1988, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Hunter, Sam, 1989-1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Hunter, Sam, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Hunter, Sam - Loan Forms, 1988-92, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Hunter, Sam - Loan Forms, 1989-1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Hunter, Sam - Lists for Exhibition, 1987-1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Hunter, Sam - Monograph, 1987-89, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Hunter, Sam - Provenance Cards (1 of 4), undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Hunter, Sam - Provenance Cards (2 of 4), undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Hunter, Sam - Provenance Cards (3 of 4), undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Hunter, Sam - Provenance Cards (4 of 4), undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Hunter, Sam - Returns Not Refiled, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Irving Galleries, 1979-1987 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Irving Galleries, 1984-1989 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Irving Galleries, 1985-1993 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Irving Galleries, 1986-1995 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Irving Galleries, 1988-1992 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Irving Galleries, 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Irving Galleries, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Irving Galleries, 1995-1997 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Israel, Marc, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Jacobovits de Szeged, Adriaan, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Jan Turner Gallery, 1987, undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Jane Street Gallery, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - John Szoke Editions, 1998-2000 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Jokel, Lana, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Joseph, Pamela, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Joseph, Pamela, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Joseph, Nathan, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Jovicic, Daria (filmmaker), 1991 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Kanter Press, 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Katharina Rich Perlow Gallery, 1992-2000, undated (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Katz, Gary, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Kenneth Laurence Gallery, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Kestner-Gesellschaft e.V., 1980-1984 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - King, Jeffrey, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Kislik, Lou, undated (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Koegel, John B., 1995-1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Kores, Al, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Koster, Paul, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Kraus, Jerelle, 1997, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Lacher, Irene, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Leroy, Kay, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Lerner, Ralph, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Levai, Pierre, 1986-93, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Lillian Heidenberg Gallery, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Lion, Stephan, 1976-1983 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Lipworth Hartman International Arts, Inc., 1997 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - London Arts, Other Litho & Graphic Deals, 1968-1972 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Lord, Michael, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Loria, Jeffrey, 1984-1989 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Loria, Jeffrey, 1989-1994 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Loria, Jeffrey, 1995-1997 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Luntz, Loria & Rosenfeld (Sales & Loan Ledger), 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Maniatis, George, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Mantegna, G., 1991 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Manzo, Sandro, 1996-1999 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Maralyn Wilson Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1983-88, undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1984-1994 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1985-1989 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Marlborough Gallery, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Marlborough Gallery - 1960s Show, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Marlborough Gallery - 1960s Show, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Account, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Account, 1988-89, 93 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Bills, Contracts, Records, 1974-90, undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Bills, Contracts, Records, 1986-1988 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Bills, Contracts, Records, 1986-1988 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Bills, Contracts, Records, 1989-1996 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Consignments, 1991-1994 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Contracts, 1989-1990 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Correspondence, 1990-1998 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Drawing Show, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Inventories, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Inventories, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Inventories, 1992-1994 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Purchase Agreements, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Quarterly Reports, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Receipts, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Reports to Marlborough, 1989-1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Returned Works, 1989-1991 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Shows, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Spain and Palma de Mallorca, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Statements, 1983-1989 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Statements, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Stocklist, 1988-1993 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Stocklist, 1994-1996 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Works Shipped, 1987-1993 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Marlborough Gallery - Works in Storage, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Marquis Who's Who, Inc., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - McGrath, Earl - Sales & Loan Records, 1986-1995 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - McKenzie, Michael, 1990, undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - McKenzie, Michael, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - McKenzie, Michael, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - McKenzie, Michael, 1990-94, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - McKenzie, Michael, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - McKenzie, Michael, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - McKenzie, Michael, 1992-1994 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Metropolitan Museum (loan documents), undated (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Meyer, Kitty, 1973-97, undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Meyerson and Nowinski Art Associates, 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1981-1990 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1981-1990 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1984-1989 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1987 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1988-1991 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1989-1993 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1991 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1992 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1993 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1993 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1994 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1995 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Michelle Rosenfeld, Inc., 1997 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Miller, Eleanor and Roland, 1977, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Mint Museum of Art, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Mixografia, 1986-1993 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. Paul's Kitchens, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Musee D' Art Moderne Et D'Art Contemporain Nice, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Museum of Modern Art (NY), 1961-97 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Nahon, Marianne & Pierre, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - The Naropa Institute, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Nassau County Museum of Art, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Nassau County Museum of Art, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Nassau County Museum of Art, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Nassau County Museum of Art, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Nassau County Museum of Art, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - National Arts Club, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - National Portrait Gallery, 1994-1996 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - New York City Marathon, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - New York Film Festival, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Optic Nerve, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Pallenberg, Barbara, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - The Parrish Art Museum, 1986-1998 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Parsons School of Design, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Philharmonic Center for the Arts, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Philharmonic Center for the Arts, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Queensborough Community College, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Robert Stein Fine Arts, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Rose, Fred, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Rosenfeld, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Roth Gallery, 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Royce, Richard, undated (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Royal Academy of Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Sag Harbor Initiative, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Segura, Phyllis, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Solomon, Barbara Probst, undated (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Sotheby's, 1985-94, undated (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Southampton College, 1994-1997 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Stein, Margo, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Steinberg, Connie, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Styria Studio, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Sunrise Museum, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Taglialatella, Dominic, 1989-1991 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Tel Aviv Books / Tel Aviv Museum of Art, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Ten Speed Press, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Texas National, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Thomas Fay Gallery, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Tibor de Nagy Gallery, 1956-2001 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Tobias, Hillel, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 48)